// File to save one response for the API so I can use it to hardcode if I need it
// and don't saturate the API call 

const fakedata = {
  response_code: 0,
  results: [
    {
      type: 'boolean',
      difficulty: 'easy',
      category: 'Entertainment: Video Games',
      question: 'There are 6 legendary cards in &quot;Clash Royale&quot;.',
      correct_answer: 'False',
      incorrect_answers: [Array]
    },
    {
      type: 'boolean',
      difficulty: 'medium',
      category: 'Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations',
      question: 'Donald Duck played the role of Bob Cratchit in Disney&#039;s 1983 adaptation of A Christmas Carol.',
      correct_answer: 'False',
      incorrect_answers: [Array]
    },
    {
      type: 'boolean',
      difficulty: 'easy',
      category: 'General Knowledge',
      question: 'When you cry in space, your tears stick to your face.',
      correct_answer: 'True',
      incorrect_answers: [Array]
    },
    {
      type: 'boolean',
      difficulty: 'easy',
      category: 'Science &amp; Nature',
      question: 'Salt is 100% composed of Sodium.',
      correct_answer: 'False',
      incorrect_answers: [Array]
    },
    {
      type: 'boolean',
      difficulty: 'medium',
      category: 'Science &amp; Nature',
      question: 'Shrimp can swim backwards.',
      correct_answer: 'True',
      incorrect_answers: [Array]
    },
    {
      type: 'boolean',
      difficulty: 'easy',
      category: 'History',
      question: 'The United States of America declared their independence from the British Empire on July 4th, 1776.',
      correct_answer: 'True',
      incorrect_answers: [Array]
    },
    {
      type: 'boolean',
      difficulty: 'hard',
      category: 'Entertainment: Television',
      question: 'The Klingon home planet is Qo&#039;noS.',
      correct_answer: 'True',
      incorrect_answers: [Array]
    },
    {
      type: 'boolean',
      difficulty: 'medium',
      category: 'Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations',
      question: 'In &quot;Avatar: The Last Airbender&quot; and &quot;The Legend of Korra&quot;, Lavabending is a specialized bending technique of Firebending.',
      correct_answer: 'False',
      incorrect_answers: [Array]
    },
    {
      type: 'boolean',
      difficulty: 'easy',
      category: 'Entertainment: Musicals &amp; Theatres',
      question: 'IMAX stands for Image Maximum.',
      correct_answer: 'True',
      incorrect_answers: [Array]
    },
    {
      type: 'boolean',
      difficulty: 'medium',
      category: 'Entertainment: Video Games',
      question: 'In World of Warcraft lore, Thrall is the original wielder of &quot;Doomhammer&quot;.',
      correct_answer: 'False',
      incorrect_answers: [Array]
    }
  ]
}

export default fakedata;